[
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_082",
        "question": "A 65-year-old man of Middle Eastern descent presents with a tender, weeping mass on his right palm. <br>- Since appearing 8 months ago, the lesion has enlarged into a 0.9-cm, pink pedunculated nodule with abundant serous crust. <br>- The patient has no significant history of trauma. <br>- His medical history is significant for atrial fibrillation, hypertension, coronary artery disease, congestive heart failure, and lung cancer, which was treated with right lobectomy. <br>- It is unclear what medications were used to treat his lung cancer. <br>- His current medications include metoprolol, lisinopril, allopurinol, aspirin, and digoxin. <br>- The patient also presents with additional pink, scaly plaques on his right ankle, consistent with nummular eczema.",
        "option1": "Squamous cell carcinoma",
        "option2": "Bacillary angiomatosis",
        "option3": "Lobular capillary hemangioma",
        "option4": "Amelanotic melanoma",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "46%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_026",
        "question": "A 13-year-old boy presents to the dermatology clinic concerned about the development of red, itchy, and sometimes painful bumps on his fingers. <br>- He first noted seeing the lesions 2 months prior, in early December. <br>- Although the initial lesions have since resolved, new lesions appeared after a skiing trip the previous weekend. <br>- The patient is otherwise healthy, with no significant past medical history, and he does not take any medications. <br>- Physical examination reveals erythematous, tender papules on the lateral and dorsal aspects of the distal fingers.",
        "option1": "Perniosis",
        "option2": "Chronic myelomonocytic leukemia",
        "option3": "Raynaud disease",
        "option4": "Cryoglobulinemia,",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "58%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_015",
        "question": "A 71-year-old Caucasian man with myelodysplastic syndrome and on chemotherapy with azacitidine presented to the hospital with 2 days of high fever and 4 days of worsening skin lesions. <br>- The lesions appeared on the elbows as “blood blisters,” which grew larger and more painful. <br>- He denied any other new medications. <br>- He was placed on broad spectrum antibiotics by infectious disease physicians out of concern for ecthyma gangrenosum, and dermatology was consulted. <br>- On examination, violaceous, edematous plaques with a central pseudovesicle were seen on the bilateral elbows. <br>- Punch biopsies were performed for tissue culture and histology.",
        "option1": "Bacterial sepsis",
        "option2": "Erysipelas",
        "option3": "Sweet syndrome",
        "option4": "Cellulitis",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "43%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_061",
        "question": "A 55-year-old black man presents for evaluation of fine wrinkles that had developed over the past year. <br>- Physical examination reveals diffuse areas offine wrinkling that run parallel to lines of cleavage on his neck, chest, axilla, trunk, back, and upper arms bilaterally. <br>- The affected skin has normal pigmentation and lacks erythema, induration, and atrophy. <br>- Lateral tension obliterates the wrinkling. <br>- The patient never notes any inflammation, itching, or pain. <br>- There are no signs or symptoms of systemic involvement. <br>- He denies sunbathing and denies any history of skin disorders or other significant health problems.",
        "option1": "Marshall syndrome",
        "option2": "Perifollicular elastolysis",
        "option3": "Anetoderma",
        "option4": "Mid-dermal elastolysis",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "78%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_019",
        "question": "The patient is a 21-year-old male who presents for continued acne therapy. <br>- He has had severe acne on his face, chest, and back for years. <br>- He is happy with his current acne regimen of topical tretinoin, topical clindamycin, and oral minocycline. <br>- He has been on the regimen for years. <br>- On examination, you notice significant blue-black discoloration confined to sites of previous acne scars. <br>- The patient has no other medical problems and no relevant social or family history.",
        "option1": "Type I minocycline hyperpigmentation",
        "option2": "Immunobullous disease",
        "option3": "Type III minocycline hyperpigmentation",
        "option4": "Type II minocycline hyperpigmentation",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "88%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_016",
        "question": "A 37-year-old man without a significant past medical history presents to the dermatology clinic with an itchy rash on his right hand that he has had for about 4 months. <br>- He had tried numerous over-the-counter hand creams and hydrocortisone cream with no improvement. <br>- Additional questioning revealed a 1-year-history of dry, itchy feet. <br>- As a construction worker, he wears occlusive, steel-toed work boots and often wears gloves. <br>- He is also right-handed. <br>- Examination of his hands reveals a normal left hand and a scaly right palm. <br>- Diffuse, fine, dry white scale was present on the plantar aspect of both feet.",
        "option1": "Keratolysis exfoliativa",
        "option2": "Palmar plantar pustulosis",
        "option3": "Tinea",
        "option4": "Dyshidrotic eczema",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "77%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_126",
        "question": "A 45-year-old man with a past medical history of hypertension presents with concerns of a rash on his left lower back that his wife noticed two days ago. <br>- The rash has been progressively enlargened. <br>- Patient denies any pain or any prior treatments. <br>- He thinks the surrounding skin is warm and may be infected, but he denies any drainage. <br>-  He reports that they went hiking eight days ago in Rhode Island. <br>-   Physical exam demonstrates a non-scaly large annular, pink-red patch on the left lower back with a bright pink center and clear central clearing.",
        "option1": "Syphilis ",
        "option2": "Tinea corporis",
        "option3": "Erythema migrans",
        "option4": "Psoriasis ",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "75%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_090",
        "question": "A 35-year-old construction worker presents with a well-circumscribed, verrucous plaque on his left upper arm. <br>- The lesion has been present for a few months, but recently has increased in size and become painful. <br>- He reports that a cough preceded his skin lesion, but otherwise has no relevant medical history. <br>- A large verrucous and ulcerating lesion with pustules is seen. <br>- On palpation, a purulent discharge is expressed.",
        "option1": "Histoplasmosis",
        "option2": "Chromomycosis",
        "option3": "Nocardiosis",
        "option4": "Blastomycosis",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "82%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_081",
        "question": "A 15-year-old girl presents with patches of hair loss on her scalp that have been present for the last 6 months. <br>- She reports that her scalp is not itchy or painful and denies any recent illnesses, diet changes, or stressful life events. <br>- She does not have any other medical conditions and takes no medications. <br>- Her uncle had a similar condition that started when he was in his 20s, but no one else in the family has experienced hair loss. <br>- The patient says she has not tried any treatments for the condition. <br>- On examination, she has several well-demarcated patches of hair loss on her frontal and parietal scalp, with no perifollicular erythema or scale.",
        "option1": "Tinea capitis",
        "option2": "Trichotillomania",
        "option3": "Androgenetic alopecia",
        "option4": "Alopecia areata",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "42%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_135",
        "question": "A 5-year-old boy presents to the pediatrician office with complaints of multiple spots that began on the abdomen and spread to the arms and legs. <br>- The spots are not itchy or painful, unless he scratches them. <br>- Sometimes the skin surronding the lesion will become very red and painful, but then the lesion and redness fade. <br>- The parents report they have tried topical corticosteroids but the lesions do not go away. <br>-   Mom endorses a history of atopic dermatitis in her sister and herself. <br>-   Physical exam reveals multiple dome shaped skin colored to light pink papules with central umbilication and yellow core across the chest and back.",
        "option1": "Basal cell carcinoma",
        "option2": "Molluscum contagiosum",
        "option3": "Fibrous papule",
        "option4": "Herpes virus infection",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "42%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_099",
        "question": "An 8-year-old boy presents to the clinic for evaluation of a progressively worsening nail dystrophy that began a few months ago. <br>- The patient’s mother denies a family history of skin diseases and reports that her son has no history of medical problems. <br>- On physical examination, all of the boy’s fingernails and toenails show hyperkeratosis, longitudinal ridging, loss of luster, and roughness. <br>- His hair, skin, and oral mucosa are unremarkable. <br>- Nail biopsy reveals spongiotic changes and exocytosis of inflammatory cells into the nail epithelia. <br>- The results of a fungal culture are negative.",
        "option1": "Onychomycosis",
        "option2": "Brittle nails",
        "option3": "Senile nails",
        "option4": "Trachyonychia",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "72%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_000",
        "question": "A 22-year-old man presented with complaints of painful lesions on his penis and swelling in the left groin that started 10 days ago. <br>- He denied fever, chills, night sweats, rashes, dysuria, discharge, testicular pain, or proctitis. <br>- His female partner had been diagnosed with chlamydia one year earlier but he has not undergone evaluation. <br>- Multiple small, nontender scabbed lesions are identified in the bilateral scrotal area and on the shaft of penis. <br>- The right inguinal lymph node was tender and swollen.",
        "option1": "Syphilis",
        "option2": "Lymphogranuloma venereum",
        "option3": "Herpes",
        "option4": "Chancroid",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "60%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_001",
        "question": "A 51-year-old white man presents to the clinic with a 2-year history of a painful, recurrent rash on his fingers. <br>- He initially noticed redness, irritation, and pustules around his nails that he thought were caused by an infection. <br>- However, the rash progressed to affect the nail bed, eventually destroying his nails. <br>- On examination, well-demarcated, scaly plaques with associated pustules and nail atrophy are present on the right second and third distal digits. <br>- He is otherwise healthy.",
        "option1": "Herpetic whitlow",
        "option2": "Paronychia",
        "option3": "Acrodermatitis continua of Hallopeau",
        "option4": "Acute contact dermatitis",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "92%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_069",
        "question": "An African-American man, aged 35 years, presents with a 3-month history of pruritic penile lesions. <br>- Examination reveals an arcuate pattern of raised violaceous-to-flesh-colored papules with central clearing on the glans penis and a few scattered, raised violaceous-to-flesh-colored polygonal papules of the glans penis and distal penile shaft. <br>- Results of the remainder of the skin examination are normal, and there is no inguinal lymphadenopathy. <br>- His sexual history includes no previous sexually transmitted diseases and no new sexual partners within the past year.",
        "option1": "Lichen planus",
        "option2": "Scabies infestation",
        "option3": "Herpes simplex viral lesions",
        "option4": "Guttate psoriasis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "66%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": "craftmd_011",
        "question": "A 6-year-old Caucasian boy is brought to the clinic by his parents for dry, scaly skin that has persisted for the past 2 years despite the use of commercial moisturizers. <br>- His scaly skin is especially notable over his lower extremities, back, and elbows. <br>- The patient denies any pain over the affected areas and reports only a mild itch that is soothed with cold water or lotions. <br>- The parents report that he had a similar condition as an infant throughout his entire body and that he has siblings who also have persistently dry skin. <br>- His parents have tried exfoliating the scales with moderate success, but the scales recur shortly thereafter.",
        "option1": "X-linked ichthyosis",
        "option2": "Epidermolytic hyperkeratosis",
        "option3": "Lamellar ichthyosis",
        "option4": "Ichthyosis vulgaris",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "81%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    }
]